<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2014-04-24T15:03:06.902-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="churydx"
        cq:template="/apps/aah/paccalVet/templates/twoColumnTemplate"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="For Dog Owners"
        jcr:uuid="aa12c6e3-705e-41e3-8f89-65cbe776bdbc"
        sling:resourceType="aah/paccalVet/components/pages/twoColumn"
        commodityNumber="AAHW-2106 Feb 2014">
        <image
            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-03-26T20:07:01.197-04:00"
            jcr:lastModifiedBy="churydx"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            imageRotate="0"/>
        <center
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="foundation/components/parsys">
            <headline
                jcr:created="{Date}2013-11-25T18:32:32.023-05:00"
                jcr:createdBy="kiransr"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-03-26T19:54:55.145-04:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="churydx"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="aah/paccalVet/components/base/headLine"
                heading="Welcome to Paccal Vet-CA1: a human level of care for the canine cancer patient"/>
            <textpanel
                jcr:created="{Date}2013-11-25T18:32:44.504-05:00"
                jcr:createdBy="kiransr"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-03-26T20:55:22.557-04:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="churydx"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="aah/paccalVet/components/base/textpanel"
                sectioncopy="&lt;div>&lt;a href=&quot;/content/aah/paccalvet/en/owners/canine-cancer.html&quot;>&lt;strong>Canine Cancer&amp;gt;&lt;/strong>&lt;/a>&lt;/div>&#xa;"/>
        </center>
        <bottom
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="foundation/components/parsys">
            <textpanel
                jcr:created="{Date}2013-11-25T18:33:44.570-05:00"
                jcr:createdBy="kiransr"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-04-24T15:03:06.899-04:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="churydx"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="aah/paccalVet/components/base/textpanel"
                sectioncopy="&lt;h3 style=&quot;font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 12px;&quot;>&lt;a name=&quot;risk_info&quot;>&lt;/a>Indication&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 12px;&quot;>Paccal Vet-CA1 (paclitaxel for injection) is a cytotoxic anti-cancer drug used to treat resectable (removable by surgery) and nonresectable squamous cell carcinoma in dogs that have not received previous chemotherapy or radiotherapy, and nonresectable stage III, IV or V mammary carcinoma in dogs that have not received previous chemotherapy or radiotherapy.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 12px;&quot;>Paccal Vet-CA1 is intended to treat your dog’s tumor. Like other cancer treatments, your veterinarian cannot predict whether your dog’s tumor will respond to Paccal Vet-CA1. Regular checkups by your veterinarian are necessary to determine whether your dog is responding as expected, and to decide whether your dog should continue to receive Paccal Vet-CA1.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 12px;&quot;>&lt;strong>Conditionally approved by FDA pending a full demonstration of effectiveness under application number 141-422&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 12px;&quot;>&lt;b>&lt;u>Important safety information regarding Paccal Vet-CA1 (paclitaxel for injection)&lt;/u>:&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 12px;&quot;>Paccal Vet-CA1 is not for use in dogs that have a clinically relevant low neutrophil (a type of white blood cell) count or in dogs that have a serious infection at the time of desired treatment. It is not for use in dogs that are pregnant, nursing or intended for breeding.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 12px;&quot;>Paccal Vet-CA1 is not for use in humans and should be kept out of reach of children. Paclitaxel is toxic to human cells, can cause birth defects and decrease fertility in people. Wear protective gloves to prevent contact with feces, urine, vomit and saliva of dog being treated for three days after the dog has received treatment. See special instructions in the Client Information Sheet for handling the waste products during this three day period.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 12px;&quot;>The active ingredient in Paccal Vet-CA1 is paclitaxel, a substance that affects or stops growth of rapidly dividing cells, killing tumor cells. Like all drugs, Paccal Vet-CA1 can cause side effects. Your veterinarian can medicate the patient to lessen these effects and careful monitoring and supportive treatment can be given as needed. The most frequent side effects are: decreased white blood cell count, vomiting and diarrhea, loss of appetite, tiredness or lethargy, and temporary hair loss, including whisker loss. See the package insert for the full list of adverse reactions.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 12px;&quot;>The decision to administer this product is to be made by the dog owner and the veterinarian after careful consideration of the risks and potential benefits.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 12px;&quot;>&lt;b>For more information, please see full &lt;a href=&quot;/content/dam/aah/paccalvet/docs/PaccalVet-CA1%20PAC-2063_PI.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Prescribing Information&lt;/a> &lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;"/>
        </bottom>
    </jcr:content>
    <canine-cancer/>
    <treatment-options/>
    <resources/>
</jcr:root>
